#### General information



Benjamin Alexander Windsor
D.O.B - 11/06/1994
Telephone - (+44) 7908 487166
Website - benjaminwindsor.com
Email - benjaminAwindsor@gmail.com

#### Personal information

A 25 year old graduate living in South London. I'm a natural problem solver and find challenging situations exciting. Working with the Adobe creative suite for design aspects / prototypes and using HTML5, CSS3, SASS and javaScript I create aesthetically pleasing responsive websites from the ground up and expand on existing websites. I'm friendly and personable and I get on with people from all walks of life. Finally I take pride in working hard and being good at whatever I do.

## Skills and abilities

Excellent English and Maths

A specialist in Front End Development

Versatile and adaptable

Strong written and oral communications

A keen eye for design

Strong work ethic

# **Education**

#### University:

Graduated with a 2.1 in Creative Media Technology from Leeds Beckett University - July 2015

# College:

Btec National Diploma in Interactive Media - Graded Merit Btec National Certificate in Creative Media - Graded Pass

### School:

11 GCSE's A\* - C including English & Maths

## Previous positions held

UX / Digital Design Recruitment Consultant - Gemini - September 2019 - Present

Consumer and Commercial Banking Division - Goldman Sachs - June 2018 - July 2019

Junior Front End Web Dev - Hastings Direct - September 2017 - February 2018

### Interests

Football - I support Eastbourne Borough and try to attend their home games whenever possible. Fitness - I enjoy going to the gym and working out. Multimedia - Other than coding and graphic design I have a passion for video making and other multi media develo